[
  {
    "id": "T5C01",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What describes the ability to store energy in an electric field?",
    "answers": [
      "Inductance",
      "Resistance",
      "Tolerance",
      "Capacitance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C02",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is the unit of capacitance?",
    "answers": [
      "The farad",
      "The ohm",
      "The volt",
      "The henry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C03",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What describes the ability to store energy in a magnetic field?",
    "answers": [
      "Admittance",
      "Capacitance",
      "Resistance",
      "Inductance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C04",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is the unit of inductance?",
    "answers": [
      "The coulomb",
      "The farad",
      "The henry",
      "The ohm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C05",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is the unit of impedance?",
    "answers": [
      "The volt",
      "The ampere",
      "The coulomb",
      "The ohm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C06",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What does the abbreviation “RF” mean?",
    "answers": [
      "Radio frequency signals of all types",
      "The resonant frequency of a tuned circuit",
      "The real frequency transmitted as opposed to the apparent frequency",
      "Reflective force in antenna transmission lines"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C07",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is the abbreviation for megahertz?",
    "answers": [
      "MH",
      "mh",
      "Mhz",
      "MHz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C08",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is the formula used to calculate electrical power (P) in a DC circuit?",
    "answers": [
      "P = I × E",
      "P = E / I",
      "P = E – I",
      "P = I + E"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C09",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "How much power is delivered by a voltage of 13.8 volts DC and a current of 10 amperes?",
    "answers": [
      "138 watts",
      "0.7 watts",
      "23.8 watts",
      "3.8 watts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C10",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "How much power is delivered by a voltage of 12 volts DC and a current of 2.5 amperes?",
    "answers": [
      "4.8 watts",
      "30 watts",
      "14.5 watts",
      "0.208 watts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C11",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "How much current is required to deliver 120 watts at a voltage of 12 volts DC?",
    "answers": [
      "0.1 amperes",
      "10 amperes",
      "12 amperes",
      "132 amperes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C12",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is impedance?",
    "answers": [
      "The opposition to AC current flow",
      "The inverse of resistance",
      "The Q or Quality Factor of a component",
      "The power handling capability of a component"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5C13",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is the abbreviation for kilohertz?",
    "answers": [
      "KHZ",
      "khz",
      "khZ",
      "kHz"
    ]
  }
]